{"card":[
	{"front": "How do you create a new angular project?","back":"ng new <project-name>"},
	{"front": "What angular command is used to startup angular server?","back":"ng serve"},
	{"front": "What is the package manager used in angular?","back":"NPM"},
	{"front": "Which file stores the dependencies in angular project?","back":"package.json"},
	{"front": "What is MEAN stack?","back":"MongoDB, Express.js, Angular.js, Node.js"},
	{"front": "What NPM command is used to start tracking packages in a project?","back":"npm init"},
	{"front": "Which angular directive is used to loop an iterable?","back":"*ngFor"},
	{"front": "What is observable?","back":"a callback promise"},
	{"front": "What is ngModel used for?","back":"used for two way communication between component and view and form control"},
	{"front": "What is the package used for connecting to external api?","back":"HTTPClient"},
	{"front": "What is observable?","back":"a callback promise"}
]}